{"id": "106", "image_id": "106.jpg", "tokens": ["RT", "@1droadtrips", ":", "From", "St", ".", "Louis", "!", "Row", "6", "of", "the", "a5/a2", "sections", "http://t.co/VJBuyc3r70"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "113", "image_id": "113.jpg", "tokens": ["RT", "@wgdunlop", ":", "Iraq", "tourism", "ministry", "statement", "saying", "it", "has", "eased", "entry", "procedures", "for", "tourist", "groups", ".", "http://t.co/elK2xwfh27"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "278", "image_id": "278.jpg", "tokens": ["RT", "@EricHolthaus", ":", "NASA", "issues", "an", "ominous", "warning", "for", "a", "vulnerable", "ice", "shelf", "in", "Antarctica", ":", "http://t.co/fAPE9tlP47", "http://t.co/WdXGVQUDRn"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]}
